{
    "id": "2fdb32a4c7124fb5ab012369c36ac3ba",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "This is the building ....................... is going to be demolished.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "88f566f1fe084ce2b0c99d4c29a92891"
        },
        {
            "question": "The parcel ........................ reached me yesterday was sent by my mother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7be9caaeee4242d79249c9165c3fcc0c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I met my uncle .......................... had just returned from Africa.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c15778db84bd4a16ae640094ee83fe65"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house ............................ Jack built it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dd735a4091814baeba3e5355051751c6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boys ......................... were watching the match clasped heartily.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "41261f91fce14881bb8670c974713612"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy ........................ tells lies deserves to be punished.",
            "description": "Either who or that is possible here.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6d70d3a8994641b98bf0f9434f669ae3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I heard some news ................................ astonished me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "30a8eb31dbe54615bf88e87d82a56dbe"
        },
        {
            "question": "I know a man ............................ wears prosthetic legs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c1e3353210184f2ba94dd6b7fd38c0cf"
        },
        {
            "question": "Give me the book ......................... is on the table.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "de9bcbf9303147b4abb84a41865e74f3"
        },
        {
            "question": "We boarded a bus ....................... was full of people.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2a02118b68594d6191ce418ea69a5177"
        },
        {
            "question": "He has a friend ...................... is a clever artist.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9958fe61b76c468fb66a0a1456904efd"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a well-known man ....................... generosity is the talk of the town.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "whose"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9454e70484724387901be40fb4442697"
        }
    ]
}